

# **Amanuel Tadese**

**Phone**: 0964023036

Address: SOUTH OMO JINKA

ADDIS ABABA TULU DIMTU

**Email:** amanishawogene@gmail.com

Quick learner with academic abilities and technical knowledge to succeed in different roles. Ready to expand horizons with additional knowledge and abilities gained from training and experience. Always ready to help others and use abilities to support team goals.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Sewnet Charity Club**

April 2021 - october 2022

Member of the club

- -Attended in-person and online training to learn about volunteer roles, safety requirements and organisational goals.
- -Maintained excellent professional relationships by going extra mile to complete tasks voluntarily.
- -Focused volunteering efforts on supporting and expanding community-based work to meet needs of local residents.

## Maxima computer training center

March 2019 - July 2019

Basic computer training center

- -Picked up additional tasks to aid team success.
- -Collaborated with team members to achieve target results.
- -Developed ongoing programmes using good team communication and collaboration.

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Bruh Tesfa Academy**

Septemeber 2017 - June 2022

High school diploma

## SKILLS

- -Communication skills
- -Leadership skills
- -Analytical problem-solving
- -Troubleshooting
- -Knowledge of Python

#### **LANGUAGES**

Amharic (native), Englosh (fluent)